Axl Cuyugan

Full Stack Web Developer

Zamboanga City 7000

axlcuyugan05@gmail.com

+63 997 976 8776

A Full Stack Web Developer with a problem-solving mindset and self-motivation. My core expertise lies in ReactJS, NodeJS, Graphql, DevOps. I'm also interested to learn new ideas on UI/UX design to improve user's productivity and satisfaction.

Work Experience

Deputy Head Software Developer

IT EXCO Services Inc. - Zamboanga City

August 2019 to Present

- Building web apps using react.js/node.js/graphql
- · Supports on designing landing pages on word press
- Configuring development and production servers
- Handles CI/CD configuration and ensures working pipelines on different projects to automatedeployment from gitlab

Senior Software Engineer

Novare Technologies Inc.

September 2021 to Present

- Technologies used: react.js, redux, graphql, aws serverless, nodejs, python, dynamodb, mysql.
- Focused working on frontend side

Web Developer

Rightjob Solutions Inc. - Zamboanga City

October 2018 to August 2019

- Building web apps using vue.js and laravel/codeigniter
- Supports on designing landing pages on word press
- · Configuring development and production servers

System Administrator / Android Developer

ZARI - Zamboanga City

July 2018 to October 2018

- Developed an android app for the company that accepts all data from the agents and stores it on theweb app (Administrator Side)
- Implements new features to the web app.
- Maintaining the dedicated server.

Java Developer

WESMIDCO Inc. - Zamboanga City December

2017 to February 2018

- Coordinates with the project manager for instructional designs.
- Designing prototypes of the project and reports to the project manager of actual status Implementsprototype designs into actual system.
- Constantly coordinates with the tester for bug fix.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science in Computer Science

Western Mindanao State University

June 2014 to April 2018

Skills

- · CSS (4 years)
- Vueis (Less than 1 year)
- Reactjs (3 years)
- · NodeJS (3 years)
- · Javascript (4 years)
- Adobe XD (2 years)
- Links

- Git
- DevOps (Gitlab) (1 year)
- mobX
- SASS
- redux

https://github.com/techuila https://stackoverflow.com/users/4778651/techuila

https://www.linkedin.com/in/axlcuyugan/

Additional Information

Projects Worked:

- Image Classification App This is an application that can be used by Hemodialysis Patients, the vegetables that the application can only recognize are the vegetables that are only can be found around in Zamboanga City and thus help hemodialysis patients with their Vegetable Dietary Restriction.
- Barangay Rapid and Response App The project focuses on the implementation of sending thelocation from the
 app of the sender (wants to report an incident or an emergency help) to the barangay, who holds the server app that
 gets all the sms messages and transfers it to their local database. The web app get the data from the database and
 displays the location of the sender on the map using mapbox and also their type of emergency.
- ExactConstruct Blog Website (WordPress) Designing a blog website for the exactconstruct team.
- Feedback Tracker The project focuses on the implementation of feedback tracking of the projectsof a company.
- Inventory Management System Developed an offline inventory management system using vue, electron, vuetify, and express